[{"topicId":"13","id":"13000","langCode":"vi","question":"Rkn3bJHZ4hqlzulccbneTxnVMvbBcVZq/id4fC6BNAsR0OXcXk9B6nNjrrQgJWNxb7EHbjMVIlnGVwsK+SvEbA\u003d\u003d","answers":["have","had","hadn’t","has"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"8zUOsyhpo8hUs1A1X8Le5KlcKdsgMB02HQJKrXaq7av6hawj9ByTlBw3ebChFmfoS6e6W7d6TvJQfUwI3yOLglg9EvxLXu3Pf1EvkMV6hgQ+ruB2h/vSZMBPiEYG+s/dXDmrnur5xt5VqKiT13vANYvvBNr3bvZQzZ6KDZV2jqFyIXKWbZRZtm2/0RCtOo7/49PWOblvxbwrl3fbM1Nr2fa4nleOq++yEiFMLCnRR2u+yfSIeWA0ORIrXUHIGlE+1GhQ7yOnbKpS9rwDOwdH+CUxuv5brhizXcc37bWkD4BeYWIBvXeDCQf5GLqOxx/k45wDr4aPlaZwDEs+vyF0/Pi2JRqAxNsD+hw+Wt4hXv44hnoYUIxviTbcc/LhDkCno+l171n7wCYCQr/H7XFLXJDIgBdaJTz/4/dN4jv8imTFxSLjFV/JpdDvyTxOWZ7x"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13001","langCode":"vi","question":"w+Tt5HFWg3KmtwkB7pJE8xvH+T3sQ+P931ONTt+O1zFxoGrR8rT8VZMmywAz7fha0Yse6NP7oEBvJoqux0rtuXTR06STGIwWVoWIcxeb45Y\u003d","answers":["have","haven’t","had","has"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"Uh8wQa394f2OiSQY2ym8GAt+NldKev9HRCTxpwkaG0PjnZkTf1QXPHt0x/57L8GHkdvKennmokIayBOX9ydPvrasKFX48wYDiGxGKxoxZsK8XYVxKsK4uHXguulzWh0IFQpLFt8PKDdIrsqMb9dT736uL6ehSA3MEI7nOba9XTAOR5VeWTNLFxYJ/w5RJPN7ralzNbTvcRlj0K2dmPhe5TK/gPWvIRBccgNUg1vHVO28o38GR0nITdvEvsT72A5IfeRdVDHifBaVwznZboJtNZ8eNyDLAKSAmfKv3yhmvrFFJ8UsE1DvDNE5l0y6ejhk7oPVX0Gw0pUXhutpdpTOfTMC//A/isRxg/3HIZASCHaVGjN1hq5ch49VVDqcnhqHkgsljypk0oxbYvLg5tMOykZCbl0tOoLeoamzDyDWnjk/dIH5eFv10z2YdHDsUv8Jrf8ZByFYYMNh+NcKS1tE7NHC/Noad9bLHw3Dza8HPM4\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13002","langCode":"vi","question":"NBj6Kly5ChoVLBHll18GAN9CES1lpPHcp11soKHcab14jMc7Qq1zB8ZbsEeQot1PlFCH14inUQIiLyaP9Vqo787CFxIuuHFGeqncpaTbAGhDrz9UM30j1mRBLUod+SH8","answers":["had","hadn’t","have","has"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"ILgJ4TU+Xtv+d9PSXw2b3qY8Iaovga3WEc38i4kmmfCikgT4pWz66RDxNmsZWXfTkLkcSxSrM2S29ow5g0/5W538Z6BJ6JqZ7SEb0PiYqlEJuiPiieLUTUFkESIAGsZdDCFPlcS8QGQsGGFFSQ84wDRl71m6yEoUvzbWwYTnhYSZQAP8St/E9f651PKvJ+9VS1135P9kWZ8xfL1xEAV7vlqBPUoRYO60c6YTu3qAO3FEy5PeZ33IMLhW8r1BkFQtVHtTl02VRehU6Wc67L+1vMc7Qgi0ScJzZd2Pc9qXndFT4ndBYCqTHlPs9U0HBcJe6vVdzcJgLegDxUuIlTwQ/llPE5FQAAc9dHYc/2HQu4lUw69H8YivQnM16rN2DNAl/9TRKosO0klQeO+Dh0O4RsMloyYInpzA1BkMfK5zQHjl3Vin6bN6twtrvDWmuMD+0PMSuoKHkfpBlby79fNfNmmuACYz1eSj+2s53Ew8TcezirU6JwVT4oaEVIXkEzk+M/DTaVF4Bd5qLLaUqP5yMg\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13003","langCode":"vi","question":"cCPgZANrhoCWMtBF4T7cRv/fGkMh0VHXqnizp28KjF1eELmkw1Aqv3MX2nTEipK5vSHfVhx0k4UTXsZ3ZiRbrD80g2F8z6oEPg5qDFpl6scCE8B0YVo9a2D9MNjgzcGQ","answers":["have","hadn’t","had","has"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"evJZtIL/G+V1o5Q+94CjCfxcOM3RN4zaLw6H+d14YGcSV0LE4xeiThSo6UXJIHpjIO6HarVL0pL0iYp6aIGx8L576IcOLSKpMbP+hCXEFt1LKgIytc3m2Sv7Sxrk8+foKfR0e7sxVxTaEMf4116RAVo2k0cLVKLH35vvSO5OGuni/u3YgQKEqQ7AWjrqKMZcTy2d1mQ6Fs6N+Y8PX30KvMBer64tckenDAtZSWNAu7V1hFLGpaCOMwu0XzsLhJPxPIaJ0wXjYrZPxkSlvBwzh4pDNrIYs3MbLxFaEeM2MKnTfX34djKhdMbci4uvE9Wcd9BvxqZ05GdNfYn2PMx2ejOzx/wkxDNOaIiXweBK0z+SYOK1cGTt7UvOzyD8d2P0pWqVEAkD8wWdON8lUiwxeV5WOcKKKZ8OMS+9NMtPlnGjnkYyLo9M3tA+JWWgPpX7"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13004","langCode":"vi","question":"J8TqUO7MRcsGIFXvKsGrHdqZHenATtoXEiUq5Kvb3XGysvRO1qp0ORwbIOnBPKYOBQATqYvSylno3Svh7WYTyOMepodorFUEhX4M7hpw3W4\u003d","answers":["has","had","hadn’t","have"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"gLkEx2nGXz+9OcWk/XokKSmqrlz6Io4Gvgk6tjbUChibrAJK7d5iuNyLIruJLgs7b3t6cpBSA3nn/IYcZJT3w3E5r2IlsW20tpGn4zxv7fRcQeiUks80WC+FcW/BZskOJTeOmxUxdRmbYDV5B756XO1RaiOdEIgNM8l5hiiVQVyDEdV3Q8rWP6XyNxWg545qdRCY/8JseXDc4MAJkvuK3xdqjUdqBTuTljvenESKluYdP5NM05SQUA8TNfEIJlEHzVcgvUtzpT9g615XyZN/Z9g2Om8lGxdiuacuzySSF29Ti704cU0W/xn6aPrYy91pvarUhA1K1UdS3eEfGR5aNEzaW8AXr+TFmO1RM3Ytlt3Ix7bazf78veODMqaFVRAvdXEGh7DabTDgMdPixrKMImbAyJIZNTjWPYb2cy07LiKEbzIZIy8f/vBQNmIt/pHh"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13005","langCode":"vi","question":"MABgjxsF/jHsYTWSVK5RepjM72EpaaGr9eeUXxdLFnKOg0Ax2UwMnMmqx3OKtAPpE17dFAOH+tH8IiG2P8grIg\u003d\u003d","answers":["hasn’t","has","have","had"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"gLkEx2nGXz+9OcWk/XokKSmqrlz6Io4Gvgk6tjbUChibrAJK7d5iuNyLIruJLgs7b3t6cpBSA3nn/IYcZJT3w3E5r2IlsW20tpGn4zxv7fRcQeiUks80WC+FcW/BZskOJTeOmxUxdRmbYDV5B756XO1RaiOdEIgNM8l5hiiVQVyDEdV3Q8rWP6XyNxWg545qdRCY/8JseXDc4MAJkvuK3xdqjUdqBTuTljvenESKluYdP5NM05SQUA8TNfEIJlEHFvCFaYJk9c5WnmKsLlJA6eOcA6+Gj5WmcAxLPr8hdPxc/Y+czWh+tK/XUSgoCjqKZrhW0VbduqsXf1J/4fDM99pMujPaXyEBgUIpzAivn3tPJ5plqPmlfKJ2y2OlNHsoGYmFwgnp/H4mGb4mAGDlkrVVDg3Yo9ro6rngSmU6Xxk\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13006","langCode":"vi","question":"Aad+ETgRe52/mi+K5uip2JtJ2liLs+wZj+9LhczQSKTQ3thTxZ9KGnSiJ2ei9s2J35DKYJheLkn924voAYGzUA\u003d\u003d","answers":["has","had","haven’t","have"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"fxG/SEka+UJO5TqFAJgQhpMk58Yy3gdsTGW2CurMI6Qg89SWDmVZAuUN3/Wr1yBrXNFLOyTIzBmGDtwpcVUhXB8VDqaDjCPzlR10pkmgJCy8JpQdfsH276628xmHSCdLCHAssmGMvGNCr8gh+FWSm5lHyAijpZFEQsVzCMiAbzzHBAFXez5qFSj0N9Q9QMZMpgHXV6nuNKgApZvd+7vThq3WWvGuwQNwF6D7+4l5St83A08cRFFWfYcFXvTO1Iv8BZ6eVVD7dJTqLwjGI3iIcJNCxPM9tGmUauDpJYoZ6WJfzOouO4O+Lwnh41UGz9Y17V9EpwbDwboP7yS+61I4kQEx6zNVRk/TUMwGmSIPwtAOdBLElkl3j/k+XUr+7WaaOahyg6QekEJPXXzZp22C9l6pz+gGB2L/ze9kueu3yFBPQIfKnnB3noHtOg61xLDg8Dfb9iKBzwJwllvSgSEHNpyrdlVXSdGc3SeyodYZOYZUE5kUVde+OLvoxlCYMiJiwaEevxXya3Kz1ASq9nAdA20sOITj5BwYwQ9rwZ8jNQomrT5aSsH9CQEp0GWeixkb"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13007","langCode":"vi","question":"Uf3hYw0asFTNM1OPu2X6Bo1gx8d0d6G2NUFPDd6pPTs/cV4CDgzZR8Ef5+u+5id4r1DpeK7L65RkLSWh407woqwm3ye+mGYmUsmYcklJHZARrRJSTf20qMxwy0JyhAUWXSKhgWTV/PdchdEEM0D8BA\u003d\u003d","answers":["doing","do","did","does"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"I8w0wXwaPiNm0r2dlgzqpHJsJQNn5kmkniHKXz8Ob0JBRekymADW0rxirCgI4mcR+DqC2K6PLRG1+nqktTG25+fsxnrmROjCsJzvnfVf8RNGyNcc646D9rpEulHEzh+mSB/KMMCZ9ZV2nqr5cD60vDIeU8v6ymLoZGZKOvDHECCYnNadc+m8OvZcqKV+m3aMO61Mps5SkN34PlJd6zNEPPa1nGAZfgmCvsOnFXBTpVNJ0E0F7SoA8+waDTxZNKrewrEgKFUglTpdUVCiXo6PBj8fvTRSKWgnrm4duBRm8USroW0spV+uH0bfSDIVpo5gnB50DKBWBbzeuG2iIXa1zWm2+XHhR9fr5HrQL8WKif9Oo5rsGMxKDaAIY3gb0psG5gDqlwtfKZ34B5sQTSgn6n0FDvc4pDBm6fuOWmFOR88P0seKPHCAgYyDGJQzt0mJ1KQ9CWarIbyW/FTLRmNQvBNi1xuOME1t5jEykY+79l0qifjAOJ0QIDg4RT9f1mCUGQVHTLRa98Z7fdHGjHEasEMi1yEwdm61VyRUgKXXPrY4kzNNVcc6iwPKWLkV7KGJSr5L2E8gYAsaf0DjbanBZQ7cFlnxyadwCflHS5UIgkj9lHm951My+Y3hXWuyeBuv2sBFvz8mzxDeaMZ7HC0M0g\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13008","langCode":"vi","question":"4YCKwFyccEPJrCpSL96uuL+/AD1pk7iYoGarJ4ARA+KHSoIYgLRVBm54VI642C5VcR1sJ12qc+UWQ5FOj/M+9Q\u003d\u003d","answers":["did","do","doing","does"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"vDjcXf7OlEOuzUGGOOaJpcVn327gMcEy+cbGJpBAFLYNALmbChT8M1V1LFRTanZT3LeOBR08mugiY9TWKaomH4ThXSpZIcF1mtfA1txbEUi9+rr1EJybcqcMQf2eEiPgEmonhClMr5P7vfBK8KHdPXzuxvOT2mQacPEonFJ9gQJ4oROuPPnak+1l8+1f0RTeZ0p+pv4MTqTZL8eyBAF2BPBsaM5CzpROqLv7gkT/hTIP6FoxibiT5TDN4uvmDDubLPs/jkDh2myXNnHnzs7hHIOh8vUczzXjtj90dTPmz3PlecJbKTGYLPq1zdTK/oKmf9Ck36hEqRyX1jRtZqFtZ/LjZ2y64pmsmfeStTRuF1ld18uTke3XzV5N4lc1nxRATfU2WIe7MlkkxsqafD9ahXv4irFkfojpoTef08mjGLVeB9mwoouqqgu2gjMCLBB6UireSBEAaV+puQxhcJ/zmPdCRIY+VpYIA1/aAatQgu9rEZHWr8ruNbMU8ZskDot8BhbqXB7Zl4yH4Mt/vfOO+qE3l4u87gM3dsZ+z/4UE9c\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13009","langCode":"vi","question":"WwEQRDwrvwwHc853Zsrx6H2/dVOBaRf4Gf/Bzv7HM9B5R4R58NL0zV7UOuJfRB9r","answers":["doesn’t","don’t","did","didn’t"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"qKORZQZZV4QRP0iuhzDAo32ErJyCr3t3PVJAjqhLVlyvCRnSvpttPVGPW2ZolC2Aj6HNYFioxRpAKkfF50IbxBnsGI1cazVslLZpGkDl0POFZ2n0EMmkzQQkA1AI8wZ3bcOR9QwMkfnRNhWYoWnHAKdnQ/6ujMDcs5tdHxqiwKDlPkYQ8bujxixl9d+4RmbZjp01RXDJLyQ2QQrzJnGII1bJQg9ZD4JF3ks2rhPxHGBxuMBgNav/JJEz25RZdDOml9nTRzWm31GLzuyHxG1G7dK/r+iZ7ze65xLd+F24MsoKZ/F+jw6F3YVZhDtW4XrM8C+19xxXwIcyP86raY6g5b/Q2/274dXgEEU32925x1K4y5jeC2DJ4ZVIjiLsgj8XieK2MOvWc4cOm3zMqCL6NesoFFJPknyYRjhKOvO5759js/gUXwinJfAlNxccxyIVl0bRqdRm0PeONjFH/3pZwMBer64tckenDAtZSWNAu7V1hFLGpaCOMwu0XzsLhJPxz0bIa/6T+kjQeJintlN2oPpkSZ6W8GdZopK5oa5GCc/hfdDEt9G1b07iGotARLHPqepCX1RFC1SvHxuO4Q2XeleCH9L9omMyL3pfbmCXqsAT9OWT19diDXGcSYiZzQZ+"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13010","langCode":"vi","question":"BDTvg/eLY5IfhNl9glh219NyXRuiGGy8xeJR4PvRV0ON+d6nLiH+c30X7c8G/k/BZgTe7xTAiyXEWOkbTewG4g\u003d\u003d","answers":["does","do","doing","did"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"SagJ9bQnmKb0O91yxBQP/0m9I5g8yPDx0yrQfXEQeEQFgCaY86oS5XrrM85u3ohGzo5B/I8mLTHbUp+v+MtLhzESh+GNW4DVEL3+ILoWxqpUrw3m/Ghv2kyQtzD1ezk8xZi3/TCHptmMJpM6CYPerxit3lXKOTdnY8jscPfT0n8ZXy0nSkYULl2TLhkJU4HLZe6zbOknrcaqQycH8mBqSD3zqGGr0prBEQcAaDlhIvsDduMH/35AZdv5wx16K29o9l6+2L7Z4OH9XNPQTegGml4CUXwFI7oHtGcwtoVGHammObpe41Y3tf86H/qQabr+B0hyuF5OkTDZUsJqGCokWEiAXpiiUZL17hbVoRl00MHdNEERcsg8dj380K+5bFJtUCYbhCQBATBLSPDRHAHtuyUm9CA4AaiSwk74xXu6bNdxF3rliwla76QNnWT7wFybVnhaY/8PDqXB0WNkAAWPPokTSO/dcw8c3fPELDpWtfFBx388ZjnVp/Zl8HlwX47SGKJRkdLQ9/DTsd/KaBsHCWBF3iLmnXP2hsZPB980Gdg\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13011","langCode":"vi","question":"60gkHpVMGXEJ58UL0lGFxEn8sfL+ZknylTkBB6W9CG+ewerUwd46EsRuCHgmrbny","answers":["do","don’t","does","did"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"qKORZQZZV4QRP0iuhzDAo32ErJyCr3t3PVJAjqhLVlyvCRnSvpttPVGPW2ZolC2Aj6HNYFioxRpAKkfF50IbxBnsGI1cazVslLZpGkDl0POFZ2n0EMmkzQQkA1AI8wZ3bcOR9QwMkfnRNhWYoWnHAKdnQ/6ujMDcs5tdHxqiwKDJVZ3e2beejA89NSBfZIlh6Y7qNJJtTTnv+6B7oZqskhDkAaVgcEqrGclWO+2WykZcQqBPUcKLDVSRD6AwgTQsUpJV6TrLNvzN+S14ol38K5ewG+edHJewf4F5VXnOsuUCh6md/gEX9MDXO337oCV4la68ljT9dAvLNhZMYt0zBwhpnqDt1liDsA5zoQFoKhGZCFn4tKOXQEQHK2HhTnYw8uNnbLrimayZ95K1NG4XWV3Xy5OR7dfNXk3iVzWfFECOCJGWQcOQwMr0oLKno5Vd+nU8OB5fweDCbHaQ77IPQLyT6BdIQGJ1c2UGAFjy7hW1VQ4N2KPa6Oq54EplOl8Z"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13012","langCode":"vi","question":"EKUIrwbQ03BmTjQgv50IVxzZObqN1zdSKvXL06RkFfbLAi4LjssCsORhGgqrrveICFOxCupc1FwlrCZByQRUGEOIGl/+z0JmeKufLh3lw38\u003d","answers":["does","don’t","do","did"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"J6ioKdJMhyrPyExqJEIcvRm1saym29Ud9378q3FaPwUNiyRe0ICb3ikgbjezhu65Rkw2ZBydVvXbHVJuMKpijD3lEu1cw1NxVa8aWQWSZtP4xqeF0lB0q/dkmlXou1CWoHGg/Vy/m0yphDeYTjJC51m/0cfU0s7vj7Bl8dPFTaJ2VE2p76XVaf0YRlGAIkS6uE4B/H7nDrMXJ2WUHbYcnSplvtqBMu3MTjsdD+sgOKD5Pp4BZX5XRt10lhLqqNYhfGQ9kPLpr0jPXq1LthN62SvUXYgI+ZPRZwtDUXo6Tx1gefcWfmQYxes/VfglXbH+LTXtEP9VOu99CeZ9bOm42DSwawiNsSL2e8LmMDLF9Pnv9Ae0Ms1M5ZmVfh/BddEQYRsafh95s+fYaqbZnO8ax8gB6upPTA0AIGVnebXvjmdEoyR2sdIjI4HeH5FRzm/j2tNuSvqv7GWX1g3mSswiN5bmj3MVoTtlWFqT4b6i/5KH+G/jYHLHNZItsdGLkSvpH9rBxpNB5ayKEoKqomV7xSYqEwhqfISg9qd7gkpe9JHo5es2i13Un/dlPlxDZZIaGAUo09hdrmJikVS8TLSShaqnP9FRfSBaczvS6ZhxoYJbbt3GGp0vYbHNjfmgbyVZ351zZ7vZ1rzvXMciKHqKiqyy6PjuD4NoSnnzYGhVdPQ\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13013","langCode":"vi","question":"F12CdfkZy8cyaNnQIgY4AUcQJ26RdqZdvSpX5SB/b8QRMiW4AI3as3qaJ9hY5M1+","answers":["did","does","doing","do"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"8zUOsyhpo8hUs1A1X8Le5MjJOuceflawzau/AsEp4OxpCAYt2RBgReMJK9xLoYTajlxihvzqaJgMkz8TvtoailNIPaSPrZLhcl3Fm/6cRcybTR7sI1xVpaoOsxlKE74uQYjdlhFpr7+kvYb5qMGs771qVNTSo6L/P+d9MkiMePTPkEj6GbtM/3us4nhLh5S2yHkhELFJsWJPGB84RdNXJXB8xac44f3LANp55pTArFDxXqsrCw6PEBKTaOsLOyCfgv63xSEtU32ixXuGtRzmAuzpUS5g6EMUToJN9QNixBUhJ4pBFZE1w2YoZlccEo5g"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13014","langCode":"vi","question":"FM2xVRu123j+KdqyJ55y78oZ6OzV7SOajtXYJ4wRYLLgavasPBbUnhr2GID8zbhB","answers":["did","does","don’t","do"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"8zUOsyhpo8hUs1A1X8Le5BK98p6gGmOp0dMjCO9PzjCx9rE0De+webBvUrC9pK3fjGwDZszlHd+12J+K7qeKjDQmTdX5v8DyqBLhDIFS4ufHAyWZTrhqGUYiIBz0MQMpaMqZMJumtZ/sHClt0XZpJaOFtMcvLs1IWq9qPFR2MsHi/u3YgQKEqQ7AWjrqKMZcsJ8Q7TEN0IWa4roknUWSysBer64tckenDAtZSWNAu7V1hFLGpaCOMwu0XzsLhJPxfdsRqRQbqpVkTZRgGe6u7DJFgpZF9kJqQjcgAlZDGuoHFwwhZ0tYiiLLbhpViuyhAuX2aM5/erJYRGXxH0zuthRvsyXAbIFxtiDI7sNdaW+9oSmmONUtJj+rJOD/GKbN"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13015","langCode":"vi","question":"5++guFzOKQxwqzmXzg/4J/wumTkKaW04OQxr2vGCs+o3A9148Mt+ZocEcXFPs4mh","answers":["do","doesn’t","did","does"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"JsG/R0bVW3+o04XNRmXgAoKfrpROJ4uCvdGzZ6ay3HwG3qj8PAAu+4FgTveOFo/sXck/72NB48/AO3YZoGDxLACEjQyquYRowncjNm+SQi1gMXmtK+uJG0PYYLcWHf8aZHvscaS7UlUYhPVw2YG45bsflgrE/Kbzfi7xmIVGlLMX/Yvq3lm0rn8gkCcoPGL3BIn29T/WVwQdK0/9J80m1uQmSRPjVskZYmqw7b5xknaNuEW/GGyDAue8JJWQEnNjuiIh7OONP+KPZw5kVTWbJhgc+8MtEP/E2jOro5Laq4VI3O2R1XekDhKkN/vD6Cn3+GP5DruSe1cHb4sVbiLjt1kmC/bdGPMV/z7F8PnJ61ou+CdFLIEO1l1AH3D1N1B6ACVHWDjj+jfGZ3TQnyCfMADQitBMhMulLulIMolTB/JpAkHjmAN24bNKqP3q7V8jBWjZDL38HizAI8ziNIdcRkPKnqrb6+Wr2w4n/TZ30+I\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13016","langCode":"vi","question":"z61t0Vw7NOS1yWM+FVU1ThAb4loMFjN5m6kts6TzqHQiwTXt77hOegOKUKc30edM","answers":["do","don’t","doesn’t","does"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"J6ioKdJMhyrPyExqJEIcvfxcOM3RN4zaLw6H+d14YGc/JwrVZIxH6DAok6YKn0icb3E/vZ5NeMUzpTTDOIpGsCjfQYvEvYk7kK7qbkNd2C2A9S7Z+YZ3x8HfxHnzb37QnDljeHnxHy9PrpqYnkeegzYLj6QdSEmr8LWMwCcSWmbMVzw1ftuFJzvffimNeaB4zn/bUGjHKLoCKQWAzPxjsyrZeqnwwxqphSW+GYMGALQkaTYpCTO7bodBpyYAsiNef9ufUzBly4ciKkLEH91ud0UnxSwTUO8M0TmXTLp6OGTug9VfQbDSlReG62l2lM59dEW5WPR03oDM4HcEclKEKSb9Ftgw37QSTZrBn8OqyhmWHCKd0PAh3r9YtU+fUp1Z2dFpAlhocWswBVLICK12qJKoTAA7oUUaOIi/E/swP2c\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13017","langCode":"vi","question":"OqdrvTWxP80KItDKssgsVlBlOqSUgDEyisAcPWhoJ2G4PMQsuKm5GNOFa/4qm8vOXg1x994mF0XKqypHg5AlM/z4ECPlZwnyWkUvdTiDSE8\u003d","answers":["don’t","must","do","mustn\u0027t"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"KC8UcFv3x2ZCuqN7atnkyfIMx9CvvajsdlsyVj4ioik+QzvU2QbQwCyZBFrkyIdJOxpQIYfkz3U96R0Q17oPzrdfs9x9Ke/9VxPQOz6tm3MLqG+xV0T6aHm3Y8FRD19fBuYhiyGia74cthe3RGUgF41oLwyJ3cNqFIwn/tNo2RwRDVileppeidDcAtwGks68A3ETH9D1Q+5tKeq8/+XPc/73Fel0z9LM3TFbZCqHmcPQfaHUySubx3FCUTMl2ZAiVJmgOB1jOOg8vwhrFzzxysjKsgP2EE5bZoByiLPBc1SMgvhSp2W5o5kJimp/MzcW4fvT0l5E3u9Pez06MZwYeen83FijF9GYzH+tyqQRa9KqvP2u1uaCetcCBrRlMGi+8TniOwotKBahomCdKMRW83s4ZHR7dmGSE6+jNJRVnZlZQ7RT6mg8ZWvZh77wJpBd2/u/QvpZwWoeRh0fd3oGQISocO66vR0zPzaJY5nryfnGViFW2rAjYIKF4IPxj1TV"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13018","langCode":"vi","question":"Wj2+L7z/5Ejc5eWxEstMEJq9/L9U/eKvPa+L8HVyawBfLqzjc74rIfn0KF4v4fFEuwXe3zjTwREnroYynH+bmJpRvG0ZWDvw2r30DKDgvRTyggM/CgKS0mWC5x36S7MV","answers":["will","mustn’t","must","won’t"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"KC8UcFv3x2ZCuqN7atnkyfIMx9CvvajsdlsyVj4ioil9vBQ4EDTf0ZbMA0WQeHY7xAZ06+vxxZm6/AUuqzBodYrp13/Xj1cGQGBW1lmUX9QXgifagAUhy+6A9mrim/hUnwU1TvAoPZ9nd2QrUaW3/4hVdhINiivvqKsGlYam+dyuf6oOR1nw7MoZUSTqfYL24VC5PwwmzRTra6cuhPPYBXIx9hsQXBgXFxMUIWXL+92zZ93Kly3mZMv60rqhjlk5cd7sTBWOdaD8IlOJCmhs29Yl3baEnf4ehkByw4rybFMTCBLwmwb9BpE1i0v3H8WTL3NFARo/mqdJf6uBGv0G1+EjsUG0Qf2c3OLiGd6JbAHXhicyv5bbitAy+ftlNqwHbS6Uxl7qhzJgB/S2cOJqnPgUZC4XVrkf+lTsZB2aaWU\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13019","langCode":"vi","question":"j/NcxBo/ifQ1cCrDEJTReM/SAyGs3RJcfwZFDs7hzo2s+Acx60JTl7ee9AcFarenLvNOCy6RWl9FZjkE25OZQw\u003d\u003d","answers":["doesn’t","do","does","don’t"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"J6ioKdJMhyrPyExqJEIcvfxcOM3RN4zaLw6H+d14YGc/JwrVZIxH6DAok6YKn0icb3E/vZ5NeMUzpTTDOIpGsCjfQYvEvYk7kK7qbkNd2C2A9S7Z+YZ3x8HfxHnzb37QnDljeHnxHy9PrpqYnkeegzYLj6QdSEmr8LWMwCcSWmYET2onstfursXkwqgN1/e79zrA58tKNKj0MnhD84jEzKRJzZxkYoP+UkgxLK6Wd1OEpmOyy5zKOJIgWL+mxfNwzbgnrA3LgHqXYHpbtG2wjwdNN3tgpKHDkc3/ZmAh46/JRmx7M/P2qwGHq8FqUv9ecHzFpzjh/csA2nnmlMCsUElhVBrnUbYqzRqOKuCGphV8teTT7BLFWHXtYgTZjGijefWuy3yh/neGci5pTKskGY9/LaweAfiJapknKa8v/a7rfS1x6c40/zlBOz0nofn+hG8yGSMvH/7wUDZiLf6R4Q\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13020","langCode":"vi","question":"DqkhbaJP2hv/+C8eV4Q6kM+5UtTsrjtPrtwaoqmZjL+PLPVhXAdNCQkbAAPB7Plagq4XtlmOHy2ALy0c7GLQ4Q\u003d\u003d","answers":["have","will","does","should"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"KC8UcFv3x2ZCuqN7atnkyfIMx9CvvajsdlsyVj4ioil9vBQ4EDTf0ZbMA0WQeHY7S/dKK+To7D3sdGme3rwLZ6C+C0059iGseJzkZ6RP5JTTRNa4SSWlbB5rF/AE+JAOHcYpytbx3J+H+L2hiThsCSHSOVrMbtqYl21y6Pj0VZ0Pyq9Q0lDdJGdCiDO7ZBBexEkHyT7IhLisjxX9uM5hPd/6CYxQeFt3VgZE7yDqRpnkLZyzmjUyAAMnzUPkwiXXGPr/6K98TV7Nk2EfJAU5JfFeqysLDo8QEpNo6ws7IJ9J5kiNnLubH8k7NPzG0sT60D47Yr7Hn/o+V/4798LL9ZOoO2WdQkxZYxt1AVpszQxYip0VMD3MiADD0WV6qOhUo55GMi6PTN7QPiVloD6V+w\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13021","langCode":"vi","question":"e4zMhC74b4oz4GFz/pjJyJ6kYVU+PnHTCnJhklQ7qYVk2/c7wbXwBrtC5ErbJVyigGmRLNWReioKZ6D2G+v9ixU34fGSksI9wyIvwh4tN4UDgNLEOGWvCOlrUO0x0Ar4","answers":["won’t","will","should","shouldn’t"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"0opc1EuiilJCrBAAXKrDi6AEtp5SGg5UeRF9G6jGH6JD1VnEW7iXhw/UXATmVJ38X1YwVuMr06TBrzMnkbNFNx02LwBTKUbbvffgk6N8cyyCNqVva2sHEqrvqBulfwG9x5Qp0lfPpem/9YpYPiajgN9llDuVnnW/wHDPlMqQ7Pmc5wjgrsVMlE9AB3NbrPoLXc5As7wcxAfsS5I3kZR9N8NBh9Twcex4ttoWG5oeXj0xY0lIbfCLRoIUXVsUT+cY29b5b4H7MtBnhgLKvvH/t/I/hbExMBnqDkq3s3iOhOWwI/W9qpvS9v5d0DsLb2ddoB3scaxzPkp5q0on4LuSZ3fyb3l10Bfte/zwCtfvnzhMnZ8TU+vTQQkctLR3hhCQXigJue+/Lu5NnQoUgjDO2+QtnLOaNTIAAyfNQ+TCJdcY+v/or3xNXs2TYR8kBTkl8V6rKwsOjxASk2jrCzsgn7aQEu9EU6byT+MxCF78DeSZbTxKz9fhp8dltpOZTB8ipaj9L6a89FRLK9ggg2J0aoqNc9cZoKbbtKU1IlzeuZlPBA8Ey/J/qa9ejTl9a4kMwm0v2w5M11JCpzsrmpdX2ZdTkwdMskQfWSrfjgNrCcCRLHSPcPJS73bOVq4YtZWa"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13022","langCode":"vi","question":"EnovdZGXg/xRUpmu5dQlyu8ycUG4ejGwsjtJETO/noOrJF4XWGO2vGcBeGfk57TJavfscGSxzWh3TEwuSTWX6VSAvsI62zeaaNO8jJscDhE\u003d","answers":["would","will","should","wouldn’t"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"8zUOsyhpo8hUs1A1X8Le5PJ8uaSZP7+EGf8/w4C4GwZP4vzc6JG7r///AK63JR+kDqPMPNPA3dgoBt4fImloXV4KA79txttyB4qfzeo7GVvnXS9Pp8tch05NT3ftXmObAB7nbkg12h3T17mQUZJnUzXlHaEicFmmI3KNVR6fQSCAblfuQ50BrTRpqeIShEyo1dR4+iI5khKDgoq5pH95FEUnxSwTUO8M0TmXTLp6OGTug9VfQbDSlReG62l2lM59g/QW7GZdRDEstGutEbE6BtoLxredeMyh0XjeEZkfIlskXgC6oWOp1dABHS1/RWe6GDE4S6sMbzlkr5OlCAnz+lMA9Q/atDAyH6OfjnFNjBqlgt2uRTmEsLMt8g54ac30Pg69uXul/G761CEzAt9JymlB4TjaZItp9PpSNDq27Zo\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13023","langCode":"vi","question":"dQzOLXmo+KIRyJAWOLu9aZ9rTMKtFsiKx4qd8JDPWUSNOnrHyDb2pZY+A7avhPkZGOgDBJ2A5DNPfGT78BdNAA\u003d\u003d","answers":["were","is","was","are"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"+6WK29ey1CgDpqiegdkW2iIzRGgG5kdyPDItn+11dId5Fl/xkg71FlujqKn/gdI4WSVRbmEuWfv50kwKAydMJ211qeaXe1gbX+0QQgx5o7VTAJop48Sy89rlsXkM+FGxMIUurPKC8PjeXeuwszpXoNoVABz/iPPWY17oYNl0JM3qwVRreWz4DjFJ1FDLgiACUVvqtO6hvv/CGa3PH/oyAGF/vF4lZl0PkgaolcSF0+HZM4GT9xojbooYG4AQEF7MR/yYkAa6P6UEBgswTqD8OqWE3Hh1aTVDk5QbzA1GbMsFDlStf5+6u/mLVa9cuWZs"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13024","langCode":"vi","question":"8JpF+O+5WrDZLfQ0LdHInOZjz/i7blajsbF/J4ZICGmhCRB6E8HB58sPDDRHey77","answers":["shouldn’t","will","won’t","should"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"qKORZQZZV4QRP0iuhzDAo32ErJyCr3t3PVJAjqhLVlyvCRnSvpttPVGPW2ZolC2Aj6HNYFioxRpAKkfF50IbxBnsGI1cazVslLZpGkDl0POFZ2n0EMmkzQQkA1AI8wZ3bcOR9QwMkfnRNhWYoWnHAKdnQ/6ujMDcs5tdHxqiwKA+MRf/8LCK2AQum/BsxDD5OBMzHWT27nFOX0S3mx2b6gyqdQmN9jLoImMXb/wDodQPoxqhbdNTNHrr4OspJvRYXEKgT1HCiw1UkQ+gMIE0LFKSVek6yzb8zfkteKJd/CvDfjkYWOvWs33lifuHRfBvpNmZlxIRF5ZJuFNzeqJe1pyKHWs8nwp0ChQ+iKGIMS+J8gyLkE41YjDVnSZ1YSQovl676LgGCY+Z1VWQh9roM7KN7AbIqj0eG9XCkgxlJ0AlJvQgOAGoksJO+MV7umzXClikyCM0CFObqW8bdJ42ucD2zb6HzYHAG27KeumwwAuKsE+Xfkwoxol/+YMH7kfDbdy0Ui/13rADIEGWUNj5UYRvMhkjLx/+8FA2Yi3+keE\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13025","langCode":"vi","question":"l5wd4fs7hZZIfuEs/egGdi7Qt1v0CS+UbDvhlU17kKDPuxEVPguvao01g/uMymsPlzZy2BlBgzkrhgLWzx0hzg\u003d\u003d","answers":["did","has","have","do"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"8zUOsyhpo8hUs1A1X8Le5AyfomPOcJnmUBjJ8O+wQVOkA/PKxZ02N862Eg+XueHq5yfNF7ljflwA48g5nE2gWMHFAkRolPRA2jq09lVJw/zy4wfrDe5KdH1D061Q+F0GyMk65x5+VrDNq78CwSng7Et0sRMegF7JHVi8ROIymMNWd+Nwwt6H4gSvOJTf+sYY/QAPeLZolGHSdGu0GwvcEc1Ecek8Sq7rdsYiD8Lk4w9Q5BR/yvs5SV7B/Gs3aM6tx5yTzik3s4QPkVWWrEASalUJDAT2g2+QGmNX0Y4BFzFRJxX/GQPnX9CsL2lBp0bBbLPfMu0NhlfB/T0qRHLJy3FKZ71i1HeuC1jmDMClyJ9lKmETZx9SGhMLtc/W8WaG"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13026","langCode":"vi","question":"OeyS4fXof+S5ISr4xghqpxEeTdolRv5XW25+uA/0mVInHPGAOkoN/OhmUOUOiuIdRWP35HOyI8VQpdUGLZvap070amLodZOsK9ZM6DPaIH5yVLP7Y6TKP49epyyn0pUE","answers":["were","is","was","am"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"8zUOsyhpo8hUs1A1X8Le5JtXzJcmIr5BfWGArva4iY7qp68TThQ76myxegk0EkEXp9f1N8eluiLProyy9KEgKMe/COnS1oDLwYfbcUjNnqTfKm8HlLOUWtzfvR+14VSL4h1GQxw6wPDDvEUJXQev4AgNoebj4HgxF4zM6ZnoI6zE5d7tvEcygPY09iMWiNzIFTHDHZuK5/ns/v1WhoUTBX3B8KOFozuqUYRNZyg0yRBnq7R940BIx7+YhFAc1L+BZ/3Y8h+OvDBUD5IVjKhbwocIkoZxDTCvrZSBeXfpyO9DLcx9KYTVVrtnShkRhg9e1tLUnJxCUIUhYhRyHhEyQYSSdmgHoXY81sHRvB4lObpRinIrkEiOiNV+shFTdz0spz0dmRx06Cgc1jQDGAEjVtKtR6+LkAfht4G4pdWIvz4+FRTIQJnaSd+c/Iqf0iwSgZt1OB98poCI5LjAcItfWyF4UXvppszqo2eaTdRxq4QvYXluahby9JRj/nTupsWTy23X4WnGrsT+NtPBjUa9c5wRJOhLGimIwYYf7vkgI5xa76gJN1AUNuwS20TxGpCao55GMi6PTN7QPiVloD6V+w\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13027","langCode":"vi","question":"VivWWGZHwQhpE/FjfPq22tOGzkQNKZh0yEb9MFZ6To1Ktm3aJm2qD8oHM5a95DzLhJApCgdIZOvbOEXL03ZeOL08CPiqosKt1SDo8HAQm2s\u003d","answers":["are","is","have","has"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"8zUOsyhpo8hUs1A1X8Le5LiOhMAIT+PXVlWEYspSgLjnLmKuEpYrGpvwUqsva7J7O/QBPtBvL+gzyl7jzCkfzZl+3ePBeLruokZCRJsuqfp0HCQn2gC1jaI51aaaqfGLZ1L0e4fHZ26ZJResvubLyDVobQnHe9JVYfXSr+SOrpzgE65VTxTgMu9jJemc2fBaTIGg4CVKYbB0Jwm2ccI6dVR7U5dNlUXoVOlnOuy/tbyIIKNhTPXpUtOXpfZ7fhCQXmFiAb13gwkH+Ri6jscf5OOcA6+Gj5WmcAxLPr8hdPwXJU3N5h8nmL9QrAfhRp0hpzho4+4q0ZUCZs/7dVpwg3F8MmCW3r9JyyUVhTtwtgmpSRQ+AxCLVzoKAO6uJ6TFYXXyFSF6MoYxDuI3v8WCPg\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13028","langCode":"vi","question":"uAi00eGIsfsyjiME1aOs87h+TTZ2HunW+OGF3fLcMgrjEO8CpfayOhKSPuY2Jj7OHS1FhhhyOLOuGK5A+eHkpX6PTLjd807iABrzsEEunSQIy2j36wL9Xkw9OZaJHt+PB3+AtFzfqfU1C3f0sjKp0A\u003d\u003d","answers":["is","were","are","was"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"8zUOsyhpo8hUs1A1X8Le5Jv3CMgWu8naHFlL4J/otdB3aHpkYIwuuRfimX2IjAl/DzHXO0kn+Q4oFUxVHnAqkqSh+7K8UmEtGPgrwdVL7lskijVFpcGK4zfIkrRGVpvAoHUhmtMYYoMypO3fUIQJX6/H1DGGssDpNMpkKjShaMTJSejFUJjHN0ThhPdr8L3NAPdCGl9Fqr8G0KVoNXLS9BdqjUdqBTuTljvenESKluZmHZdYTfcejmRKeQBerD8xdMUy365fmJRRB61Zo3m9Gdg2Om8lGxdiuacuzySSF295TLzVx//GHZ9pGOPoWZuHLTeIDiniT7PwQT9yGTpW78sJ3PYH4w79bbiEsXYxInvibfsskSVpyWoMoWlQzf/AvUK2BUvXB6RH0ZlGQUI9qmfo425Znlglw9pTMeXceBjbu0sTo5Pz6moHw9QgJxrsz5IQOelgnB6HlKLEREU4y2Wy1Q7SEA+dkIAypuB+zkuEbzIZIy8f/vBQNmIt/pHh"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13029","langCode":"vi","question":"lzdD8st0Idf0fKYTDHqOQUvLxD/XcqkNk1SISC3XvI9Vxu+7kAukRCiOW+d6h8CP7jm84Kgm144aOx2R0SO3EQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["do","has","have","does"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"8zUOsyhpo8hUs1A1X8Le5IdnRT67EtHzwvsZyEHZdUGyzZ2j/I1WBguPHwtNth3IaSfmTKhakN2po9+UDoni7deO02feC7fVG0ICHrjRnreR7YksBaFfdGKaeX/MCsCdfOugz+EteXnENhAgoC03gu+CQuhz7OP/eeXMw3gtE0rAFAc0VTniskHuAKqtW+ZmvHTuwlg01/+Y4R32ThM04RMLQk/+LdzQke1JyYebwMibTR7sI1xVpaoOsxlKE74ufZJrpgrgZViGm4EFPHer3LgidrOIBdvCILTjvO7DVdVnDL4L3+NwusIxfj01rc7iy48eb/9C+czR7qzoscWdYt/lCwwMg7WKB5HOKyMD9+fbw6D08cwTVOEzmhwua352VALMVM8GSPGsivJthNqGScypberTeV4B/aC8FriEMz7UL54+nmiLpHsoBXgzV6Ti"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13030","langCode":"vi","question":"qe9Sp65MukfJ/nY95t5GqL3dXt6+FINkaA5anrNHDOyjPCWrneB3J7vsB+yMc3BBS2dACtRJiqj5YcCV/Spu0QrNMziNs2/C9dx3++eE+2Q\u003d","answers":["am","will","is","are"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"8zUOsyhpo8hUs1A1X8Le5KtrGSMMue+mJND1LA1HiHBV853vVZXZWoFoinHfNXHMpTsid5/XLVYKnm21+VaH75/scMlGhs5UUQtTT8oqYoVWJYBBWWOxUmMQkrT2XD9A4Vq25mt31JzfMQc6tpzEGgOdEDYbaS5oOHoG4D2oN6IM/g3eGC/eN1oDZz5PMT9mSp/d20M3GXunuoQvQ6NDCEuRVMoYDBOZLtAHkwR3E78OdBLElkl3j/k+XUr+7WaaQR0fFjferCpeLPO/rxX6YF5hYgG9d4MJB/kYuo7HH+TjnAOvho+VpnAMSz6/IXT8QX4nSuwDbUzo6lANDxPjpFq066q/o6xzKjUl+gh+VnynNOWl9FDHK+189WKjhIwd5PTThizg2ISM7yNxYJNc0QqkUJNDWU2JfmubtEj791D6PC1AvTWUPgLWNXtdqOAsJAnKFqGZtAGO5lLNXQ3J/g\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13031","langCode":"vi","question":"O9sGGKOL/0ImlwDzGVXL267cp0VJDp5uH1h71E52fW3E2ogHDl4+kRubOhl/QBhw","answers":["had","hadn’t","has","have"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"AkH7GrzXm3PRejvJJie1k58rSOsxs6qTzEfHypTAGeGvH//W4lj5XbvLa2pf46BJC+jpxokv2YB1aPMR39/Bn/OMwMboKkP3bdu516dj2HOoIsM2aBF7jcDAZHi1F6jdVMqw5kXuLznCX8cGzbA36vuJTCuuOr/6tL2HDrBrF3BjIX8wYQ/KR3PlaOQIVOMBPorm536+30LssT4L7kon8sAi0EjyprSPLbrWCjC3wkSwIjBRgqGLQp6kdKHtMGw3CGmeoO3WWIOwDnOhAWgqEYKldDed6RmSpxkTcRYo5F/q9V3NwmAt6APFS4iVPBD+WU8TkVAABz10dhz/YdC7iRwINswmTbkYCyvjG20kYGzUokOZePj6znlJ118iOAAtsfeWen8BVzgSelhYn4QKOAGEcJAAAiMvNcjJGrukSs+vIALkf3ZmDATGng6bA1w/BQrsCu2g8RCOXvT5LBVQ3AVfEAfnusSCp9W5zTSqEZI\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13032","langCode":"vi","question":"9vQKPRaWeZ8qo9byObiKFTLeCMzRyq75MvFT4UJb4axO/6iQTS3+goiOtV4tangxBjDEnW3GTquLtcAV7UKJgtkLsd6LGkLUJtbJ50sDSrFcAtu/LI+zdqSwkW+/f5tN","answers":["are","was","were","is"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"AkH7GrzXm3PRejvJJie1k58rSOsxs6qTzEfHypTAGeGvH//W4lj5XbvLa2pf46BJC+jpxokv2YB1aPMR39/Bn/OMwMboKkP3bdu516dj2HOoIsM2aBF7jcDAZHi1F6jdVMqw5kXuLznCX8cGzbA36vuJTCuuOr/6tL2HDrBrF3BjIX8wYQ/KR3PlaOQIVOMBPorm536+30LssT4L7kon8sAi0EjyprSPLbrWCjC3wkSwIjBRgqGLQp6kdKHtMGw3CGmeoO3WWIOwDnOhAWgqEVy7Yl+ziOtIHq1cwaObZrI\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13033","langCode":"vi","question":"2LqzN7z4PsAnTeF6TPbVHbgqwhhfvoJSRXADK8vlZgrKKFu2ORE0KXl77EX5NjpXOeQM+GFEAIdHaiueA9v4A92AQP9J+1PdAKtFhiXzb0g\u003d","answers":["has","have","had","hadn’t"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"plOu44NYoDgNWVme9AsqTgCmD0ut0LxqwnTwx4yvBBKfRYYFAEWX4uo4Jm+McHuyLZ9vXfwYlLTNicci2EIzaezsFODOj+o7WIPCVRuHWu0wgdSxIDTJ2C2qEyVLqWxN8zUOsyhpo8hUs1A1X8Le5Bh+Zw+4ATVMvn3Vbx0PdnEKyGKIRaw5KFZiv7LsFtZtDCFPlcS8QGQsGGFFSQ84wERxrHwEJyKQSeiFyAgltW6xA4dTK3BEqmzkMvsH064ShVpwRP3VVB+wDidnM4F1Jpc1d8dsRlnfGZ/phBwu1SzB41GqqWfdLvEWrKruZ/segws7HHdyGZutaRX/RYrqg3gTnVD7N5EgttXhH490eh4Rux7kZ7EjZxTGHlIVOSCazTNhyBRmjr7+t/Yllgkkis24J6wNy4B6l2B6W7RtsI/j6HUO+xDboKTqY1whj7Ydh/hv42ByxzWSLbHRi5Er6R/awcaTQeWsihKCqqJle8Vvo7n7RfJMoV3pMTkVffgUSaxyXwceu+ViAKg2wUVt4Ivsn6WasonNwGqQNRMXU9iyhoRlf/g2pPCQRJrgpiJob9yDzXCDRAI5xrE6/HQFKidtWJ4nNupzABjiAf1+nPjZWL+4w+NJOz3rrXr3XFD8"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13034","langCode":"vi","question":"gAgcjWp3lLBPiRAU+WMlKVPow1lGUMneT8rJlk7cH3TP2t6M0HjUY4gHYmwfEWvk4mNltMV9Pw43OqPgrnEdiA\u003d\u003d","answers":["hadn’t","have","has","had"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"8zUOsyhpo8hUs1A1X8Le5Dg25Zz6tgaaeyd3ovBYds6yDkOVt54odqfXjOU4AnNglV2aqnmDtEYL9bzKnU4LXc1Dp3NV2DQ+Xw9fE1xo+24SpIuama/EelhLYH+60QefNdoU9ubN+7VMBHC2ua3+gpLla+e8BQKgwwVHqMKVy10c9uT6J/gi/b6hO5+lNfPWJGhVNYH1V1RoPaEIU7UVUDctfvkpRHjURWbrOfTWqUjG4e404qYFG2pJn3Oyq1duUOQUf8r7OUlewfxrN2jOrceck84pN7OED5FVlqxAEmpRfzkLgMZ+/IKzyInO39kX9LAu9YUH8v9/7UnyHeeKfcgdDmp6HsJt7XoRCJ9eY/OAZCN3XqI+H/g8+T0pDZY6sCE/CxNxvJSS5ejtVCjRkA\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13035","langCode":"vi","question":"mcWBSZ2pBclnLINNhlCci3whYdm2U/YPu+WJb630hBjAksHu00mTHwvAScElRFsVXG/Bix7G7wH25vSH/fd0YQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["should","will","would","won’t"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"8zUOsyhpo8hUs1A1X8Le5CC9SNk3N1V1IRm2/7ShoQMuqOod3r/hiiCknbdaZTamfEFIB25dgxALhrAIImJZqf5OcfvfDn5EpmrQ3dSnxlkcefDH/SRf6Dlh5k66EEb3m6WMdGuv74hIhwUu2zpWlHeQKiRabc1K/MhzTgiV2vH1rXE7Y4RCyvHZF+QeZpVzfd5vmUQgVnj3KcussJw2GhWdpNChvSyB5AHMu81BqdH7G2dDrjsrVcSbM55gPfMjvplGz0UfXU6F3NhJRYVhFQqdFqMwuNZsHwIaJUO9BDZbarb/jBEHmOao7jae010nY7z56jPMWhAk8U2wT/DhLA6eEGb5dLMV1n8Cef6NySBEoyR2sdIjI4HeH5FRzm/jVHtTl02VRehU6Wc67L+1vENz+fU8UDgGx2aUFwsktFxFJ8UsE1DvDNE5l0y6ejhk7oPVX0Gw0pUXhutpdpTOfROdCjnh/QUCLFAVzo8cFLYFu7rx74snlGjVHqey/vXMVR6PxwTCvOlVvXHIohjL4c0GqficoZbpWfW8NMXsrpI2u+wpCI73xQv8sF1qQg9sLf/PiDBDKxfATG+rRkHGDA\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13036","langCode":"vi","question":"AaRZ6cRhlO3pyfiAnudCSWkr3luyYCDKozaO3dwMZyXzbIs+BkxzKnhq4xgDF9eGUCdNoZkLqIwwW9QePAQqrX2+zdCR/isI2DuVXtVGMO9UgL7COts3mmjTvIybHA4R","answers":["will","wouldn’t","would","won’t"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"8zUOsyhpo8hUs1A1X8Le5MwYybcHLAQGstwmCtK2F28d/uursZySgxDpY+sG0zVdG/apwColHoQoNp4pYtit9Lj/49vsb9PF970IP8Jkp9W3agD5F7XDCqgquVm+LFU92uk+ZAxEjRtScllSscfciV+wtAi75FHtYowVWyn3x+abJjfdse7mW2dUKokCiGWH4uX37atAlkZhXO562m7GNPHQA3FUnWklGpcyoeJfcYU5UqWNDgVHlqCXzf0aaN1d7bUCwiovVZswcrRIw7Gasn9BPaeL+efBu2bRtoUs/NZjk+y/V/s/IiLcJ4N6VRylxW3l/p36R3inybXX7wFNa4z8CP/1uypi4KN7OH+sMwGIg6uOdwDxiauGiHKaGMvSVnfjcMLeh+IErziU3/rGGOzEaw4GosOX4KAb1slHpam53/x7Y/0mdoDoFZLA6cCJJSb0IDgBqJLCTvjFe7ps1/yCFUB7uh3ubVN+HdVwFnwvokl46han/0MYzceyhxE0Q00kDGUXj+L0BAwPxs3jXblFr/g1Wuj+OMzi8sXTauam90pxdDe+b5xasamlGdzkJ8MZMrsI9RmwYcHQeDuHzekj+0DS6EtxqmOaqZLuOj8\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13037","langCode":"vi","question":"9UQdR4BbFNTq3zLsytXgg1wwOZGwZ0Jf2Sb6NW8T9FZPDpnpPOD3QPMO+ujKHo6wRDeoWdOObQOQdE54iuQmAeEbuUZjz94vRNdQ/QYhnf3ZcQQB8v8tSUonVT7GOvQv","answers":["do","are","is","does"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"8zUOsyhpo8hUs1A1X8Le5IMRJpU/aNzfM5DKDlzMedJNoXZ4C94nPBeO6F1QL75qBv7SMoSCQW6wFyUSfY+ufyiVFWCvFPvmNYGbGnL6SDwy22jBB0qzBF8f/wau7WZ8IO9Euyf3mu629sJHCvYkW49/Ax9Kjd3V39aNvV2krusNYdAeY8qZT/5uSsNNY7H7pMT5xshx98KxIXvEE0aOwye6/LDdUIZyPQfMwHeEtRAXao1HagU7k5Y73pxEipbmxrrcTkR65R3noce8JMmNq81XIL1Lc6U/YOteV8mTf2fYNjpvJRsXYrmnLs8kkhdvl4a3ktxKozWVuq+SiGrUDHYSX9xNhstA0cX5Ycb4QyjkjczPwC/rbF/5+PZsrWKS18ysjMbWD9wJ5LY1Ql2OapyWQvbQ9s+Ki0mLcBpIaMwhE+M1fcgY4cpSsf0HAovY+LVBfLhbO6aO2KbTqs4+Ladsn4i1m0o7Zngy5hxNXkTK8f8/mMrdRmOXJVj0TTrIo55GMi6PTN7QPiVloD6V+w\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13038","langCode":"vi","question":"99qqjUzJCRpDBU13ZQszx2FUGPJfFmkRYa4JiBDsCWvsyvDFiotJCZbml4GA6zsPA1qPWsHDWzBQnWAyjh/Bog\u003d\u003d","answers":["were","weren\u0027t","was","wasn’t"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"mck4wNtNq5tqZQjKMQMmlCI2mqlBQUiz1hZsKNdsCU8+ZVhQPz1Qsf5+o4x77gc+A+Gy/VyF8tANStJuF0RZ0tirNBdis9zu/By1A1aqeW3ed4v9CIzK8LecseuFojK72343P+fih919l0hRL/rcQ1Z343DC3ofiBK84lN/6xhiVryOIOqLUynsghkk8GhV7t58IM7gCiGP0PWPVChY5x/LjZ2y64pmsmfeStTRuF1ld18uTke3XzV5N4lc1nxRAe+9pZTFe6WcMyGyPiz7nfF2cbjyEgQrrug8pWSeLb+NSiJhvY+6HDtrGvnQnpBAnGDhZhA3isCS7y6QrZ/k77cO1kbkNQDJIWd4zq51b/o4IxFemDRP9JZvMy+l8RiaH"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13039","langCode":"vi","question":"vFkrTA/IKy/KD8y0+RIqy/54WPPaDYm2Clt3O8z31ot7WunZLBwLkaLJXJjGM2M/","answers":["is","do","am","are"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"YDF5rSvriRtD2GC3Fh3/GlppuysG7KEtM4BasLZygKJ/dF5fBC5fEhQf+3eY0RLFTAky2kTGws2VnWgCckCMwEzOhaeE+EL1ztkKQc0bqDHGax6+cR4dLEEd76pM5YtE6W+ne+rxB5IasfQNoCpf+Trk6z3AgKWvD4kc8hadnDrCsy6JKUbScRsn2DFC7ILpL5ZJGCeZjSpZhPPlKAjaWFqhd0rCFZnNRIns6oQbPvNBdb8Jif6nN+7TToBTTzUHqTldlYuxEJfFPo8+TvY+AQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13040","langCode":"vi","question":"4dHvcHeIZfumRsImIKoZoYy1jiPGfOQ+vQlGxQJz1XF6uU/LfoZxYs+wj76hupmqyLDkg1F75T8FA9op0fDr1YTRs+ETA2c7d9TiKRfhuIY\u003d","answers":["hasn’t","hadn’t","had","has"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"8zUOsyhpo8hUs1A1X8Le5HOKWDnjt+214GybfNyVzmREnJMZybikkAVs9A7uniVcOO9bDCbYQ09mLXGVYPFvBOXw08d/EPg8lbphXy4NpqeFt32TjxEkCUWKX+dtSyb+gJBEq/Jp35wmzOqgs0U1mhk0jGxxFoXyCEQ5cXl7TIW2V58IIjaVme3CDMuxy3h6EBgt5+l5UH96ZlcradeVsrlhnGfBzj56C5o9J5AgvXkXRz6xYZqp8rvmb/A6SWaT+WEs91W7GAhEW8BOAFDEL3eapeP1SmpFgpt/r0HmamZvKZH37a7DZMs3buDSROS8zd/VVPsnYTiyo9c1vFQs3KO2ne1UaBb/cgIekeVoCmaIz3+cPIGhSO/b9KEb7WTqcibujHzEEqmiQIZjnL2XHDXlHaEicFmmI3KNVR6fQSCAblfuQ50BrTRpqeIShEyo8IT7QB3iacpOE/viAHAhNRCoVI4MWGgl+NwFR9/tvQEZZfoowCXvo7orSAPr1HONWMRHua2+/StIfOzCDWcaTUwlPOSQqpy5SjKsS+7QYb1n1T9Zs4wG7bMdmaJ1pzN2R7o7NqBo8Pd5CczZRXaJDCDGAOmTHhjzwoQ8bgIUqvK31Elb8OkH3PBT3WveXVNI8yGRP3zcfdTM9bwxhJNTydPRwmjTdbZkSoorIN7Mo+52bbXng96x/Q9hgNFWs7B5"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13041","langCode":"vi","question":"3yfvSzOaArfLIVAxkqa6TzHNV/nf/6dXkoGtbbtL86KApt9IJdru5Avgzy4+x09yId99in03EO1bslclLRXr0g\u003d\u003d","answers":["were","are","is","was"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"8zUOsyhpo8hUs1A1X8Le5FhlAHPzITHNEpjb88PoNQN6aSCp3UaeB8xmRPur83WtpTsid5/XLVYKnm21+VaH75/scMlGhs5UUQtTT8oqYoWsNay2WGKt6DQV6H9bPk6oFqACQqTGQoXJAEuvVo7VuHfGCNKsQRulwfltPVB5qP93hw/DmuB5TBEgKb4r4VzGBJD8Y0BT7DRMFJ7T/thEGfcH0TNKZBZqNFlYESBXTr6tLy1WE2RI8f1/IeD6b9QGl5ky3zXof37T2v5TnU6ejVb+TzKsgDygeqmvu1qdjlBjiPtshCFvVHM21/ePfIBq2DY6byUbF2K5py7PJJIXb69dJxmxU3GzGPIjAAmgshrGHfbNpjYTrhQzNukVMlMjNvgl081/SnDB0taLwbrISBxz4FDaHaKmx45jtkJNSeSgeWnzWhKi5gaApAraOYBhrRusYSm+XWZHs8F/cCCV0g\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13042","langCode":"vi","question":"xOaqDc9DybdNpZ5ox/oKyUI7ZVEOlfguSfRLxZdCfvoTngZlcXrBnNpbnvZATCBu","answers":["were","was","is","are"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"k/sB85NQFGEihuJCqhULZGAxea0r64kbQ9hgtxYd/xpaabsrBuyhLTOAWrC2coCiHa5kHNj9hfLJ/DuPTd41xbGzX7TfnlroJ3F4staqRc8o2It6ryx817ATPxElZc1Ogws7HHdyGZutaRX/RYrqg9rDdRPebNiuqEW1REb3ExY6Ci+2NvWtc1tPtcJ2ZvTtSIBemKJRkvXuFtWhGXTQwQnfTPGKCKNBWb/gJOEcux8+s+VxfzZunN+DxNEm6XKKh/hv42ByxzWSLbHRi5Er6R/awcaTQeWsihKCqqJle8V/A4B72571CuuLj7ufgR5bLTO7tpLnfA9R6VQ89QI9hYhBk70XHs4yQIESNTTbuICjC4rDFGNUewSh3ufq5yjA"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13043","langCode":"vi","question":"gvE9PfglVZ9VaUtZWygw87lLnqNxXvHZ94uyslZd/mvy9bJjxvPhySNOcC20TcnJ96H7TTDK8ADZH6XbFEV+klRMbfGnxgCKzLR+Igftoyg\u003d","answers":["were","was","are","is"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"8zUOsyhpo8hUs1A1X8Le5LmIKWs0DTeOXbgz4xhqd4xXG2gIpNVV3UegrvEcF62Ea2B4QDbmF5VbarnO3c1tPt3ibcOOfTrfHrswY05q8+qk0pH8Af5sKikj++4+bYsT5q6kW0zFH0E4UetbLeEppHZ2wSLa8WNqHXbBsE4Y7Er0L91jtk0cAsvyw+yJGKS0bRh6K8J+KAzLdLzcRuVRoGgBeaxYqI5Bn9eKUQWt5ML4Y/kOu5J7VwdvixVuIuO3CL/wVQiAehU7ocO46zc0I+r1Xc3CYC3oA8VLiJU8EP5ZTxORUAAHPXR2HP9h0LuJWhe3bSROeBWIpTPFKcaaRYxd8/2eRST4U5s5+e80oSXq7CPIpmSZobt6UcLjiRkQ0yrguJHpn/+M8LaZVDDkFLfQcVqYNcvkalV/+QyIeF9zwZ8rynXq8CJ7mnv2bGdh"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13044","langCode":"vi","question":"yJEdFM4Q2YN4kVGJQGaktBSJlpHVEnMFdO645vG+D3UXX7JMZu/07q0T6oRCqBjnY1qbgfg9gYUrG54oVJX1Xw\u003d\u003d","answers":["was","were","is","are"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"+6WK29ey1CgDpqiegdkW2iIzRGgG5kdyPDItn+11dIchcP/CoX2h3AAS7q1cbeMrlEJGAjD70ouT7EvBVivXKWdWtFSNdRzCXRh2j9pkjg9TAJop48Sy89rlsXkM+FGxMIUurPKC8PjeXeuwszpXoNoVABz/iPPWY17oYNl0JM3qwVRreWz4DjFJ1FDLgiACUVvqtO6hvv/CGa3PH/oyAGF/vF4lZl0PkgaolcSF0+G5sjXA+fPBYvJLYz0iafgxnwlvqUr4DUWKKD08/JW7uc24J6wNy4B6l2B6W7RtsI8dZTtUEEW71aEPvX5o+gJ3h/hv42ByxzWSLbHRi5Er6R/awcaTQeWsihKCqqJle8V53VB6wG5/oFzAVogAcjk8Wmwt6UxBq+Wuj7yZOqLQxRX6JPwooVKk3RTTditYRYS1x9XWtpc/hFI50QMw7ujHb3HQT0nIje3k8GwiTl5U8lptdAqeh33MeTUVwZhW3V8\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13045","langCode":"vi","question":"u2MqpOr3WuaqKxHrv9P9+Xp/8IDZm5a+DWPRasJOIKRTAlh3wAAfvsMzuR/P97jwOFB2kScsh/wiZkjmvK/FVTFJwRFsnwsjuehLro0ldlk\u003d","answers":["do","did","don’t","does"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"+6WK29ey1CgDpqiegdkW2iIzRGgG5kdyPDItn+11dIchcP/CoX2h3AAS7q1cbeMrlEJGAjD70ouT7EvBVivXKWdWtFSNdRzCXRh2j9pkjg9TAJop48Sy89rlsXkM+FGxMIUurPKC8PjeXeuwszpXoNoVABz/iPPWY17oYNl0JM3qwVRreWz4DjFJ1FDLgiACUVvqtO6hvv/CGa3PH/oyAGF/vF4lZl0PkgaolcSF0+F9Q0tZwbslO0pqZWzovJx48tyl0S+jGmsNAAa+iExcOIOh8vUczzXjtj90dTPmz3M8HVlPweguNLSfSIYtzKrKh/hv42ByxzWSLbHRi5Er6R/awcaTQeWsihKCqqJle8WXwMbKiRwWomfbGDan0MIcBFflgCinzQNrpXT7zNJhLUUTeq7emI4imuK1KtymLGKtytMAeCZCtR/xZWp/yg0m5VNqPqC+167yT2ZDk/v0Cg\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13046","langCode":"vi","question":"0oSyK+9Z1MjgymEyo+6+Vw3uzwfxQQFPfduam/AA1eQFDMCw5f1EU0YF+oEtbiVf","answers":["is","was","are","were"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"8zUOsyhpo8hUs1A1X8Le5IMRJpU/aNzfM5DKDlzMedJNoXZ4C94nPBeO6F1QL75qBv7SMoSCQW6wFyUSfY+ufyiVFWCvFPvmNYGbGnL6SDwy22jBB0qzBF8f/wau7WZ8m8usP6wNSLywM7VLL/v4GjctfvkpRHjURWbrOfTWqUgatMJELfx4PigTZcUslYHI5bcwYV81Kcb+c1KJe9AZT9zDmDWwAJTDAwj5RiIEVac04F1YlzQwyQAc1DS0r5wX45wDr4aPlaZwDEs+vyF0/CWE78TGvAOdtUdLWsf4soyjML+Zh80A8iNcoaK++7BG5VxCnCJGKHd6ZHH70GArUrVVDg3Yo9ro6rngSmU6Xxk\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13047","langCode":"vi","question":"reZ0vX9FfKlGafpxavFTh84wZ4RZV478TVfoa5s3WdNdtX3vKP/l6/8AETV2z8kMhG8yGSMvH/7wUDZiLf6R4Q\u003d\u003d","answers":["are","was","were","is"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"oavsGsoaY88v7piCIQPOl+dd7X36Bu2BP6Dh0JAuXe+DgiUUeDefE7tePXLBsJF2fkd+GdjgX5pdmtfHoDs5VvO3g6Kyr55wy8IjknXlxNroOGfCGx2759U1Xi7YFM0Y99mDppHcq7WdjHVNOhNl5goqKs6FO+WZ0gexIoiRd4WsFddDJpTwFnltdeUgaH9dwtO8Xp4ORSVsG/A4sfAi4uUDEPj2RSTR9is4WxTDOOREy5PeZ33IMLhW8r1BkFQtyI0HMS7Q9Qnw+ye4AAiPWWI+BCF7Wfz+ue+DZYDOvj+nPR2ZHHToKBzWNAMYASNW0q1Hr4uQB+G3gbil1Yi/PtaHBxgOaBWYsPadhkKqWqNGD0Hs8ziFmadkx1aCfNAaYtAEANfCNylxmIFBzY2d+m66B69GLZW2xTKPHzIoUR1MmuM7b9Q4HxkY0qxgu0yx"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13048","langCode":"vi","question":"WvT1LmUBJi39rzauiSXPQ6RZ1cebIgxMwNHY4uAsip8CNr7pKwJ63BZnt8DA0HzzFAaIXxFeYILcltvQLp727NTbbBvTm+7XFfxzSbXpSVaehFy0Rp+zM2j6YYi9r5W8","answers":["is","were","are","was"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"8zUOsyhpo8hUs1A1X8Le5Dxw9H4G+5U1XhSGJdciLr/U0x1unB0w4fKYNxDjOD7wv3EMoHdObNkp1Z4gnfnP9LEDh1MrcESqbOQy+wfTrhKrYdb3lHyE7JxDIDVcJDCpz8yd2iQLHmWJlovV4/D+QFb8ti4UeK0Tg0TsqZBh2dIlRMdkWfyxCU2A6hqBS+yAtSLLFp9aAGF8VrMDI3dDQg/ddLgvbYL7rkTXYx9dBn8e72xtSVX8anU2iExq5mDdzbgnrA3LgHqXYHpbtG2wj++hoKDBY+tcBQ0vO05xAxNFJ8UsE1DvDNE5l0y6ejhk7oPVX0Gw0pUXhutpdpTOfUcZvSG8Eyh5lxd9cp91Ct7M1B1aFHnID1kiH8rJj+JZn1fgXJr+UZW5tpeJSRsKGRQg5k1yQKqZ3FCYZrIBM9bkDYXaERHALrxXYg9njpNVyzkWzOVxnkLtHPNc9sf2S1MX7mv/XAvORj5zS/Iu23OFNfPL4x+doz7bddqpG4tB"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13049","langCode":"vi","question":"BZk9uw3x+fy4Z0cKvtlzgbBtiZi9Whep6y69PaHEFz+sG8A9uBAWZyrWwLSjcnSSZC8vPGELgxODE9tlO4yUERZNVNuL+KXvnyH6O/7knYBsYkaWksOATELkIJ8Z1qjV","answers":["can","must","mustn’t","can’t"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"w6cIbtkIwSYfb4h7qFiNxkmdfl+rh8ZCRbyCrW0+U6SiLhOt1JfUC1fEFh9rWyOui3TRwI+IxnPOEQ+hBsnRymnaWeDJ8qkP5pElVIlDqKvqaVALbUMWAek3aD2qsuIJrEHtPvefNF1/X5N9dc9bPcP51Y6ngq+CRBiHBiApoRUTzFpxmqtsQZZ/qc5EvEzEKAfzv/V3nDls6t+3wa8lvG2DDlMzOeYXB45c6gaBf5Knh0Zedh4SxKTmh6LhZxXM1shVJcSq6XqEOpyGIcsMdS0PDqPKxFks+oIoUeSfg8T/3JXOtOQH1NFcmzdNDmzxdAnJa3oiofN6+/oqwbDaKML7PHzSfJ42/TkpFW0ItKMJwmXBZLzWhgqZByMdK66eUYtxuHyS02fEuilepHWqmSwOmkfGTGz8eXwFBTyn6a0NjtVs+Ij97JvQyctc+ES8XkKqQRsi2I344Y/POm8175O2sE+JJkH8E1dYTmSoLgojJVn0jSZBTWkMa6TfFDn+OuTrPcCApa8PiRzyFp2cOr2rUdBnGRPTd1qJquzcU23WEWPbZcWiqWzK83PPoO0wJdR0jbHzaoPZqzaHI67xpklk1sGB8MmOUepFONxkXbIylFsPdBX084TGZXwRGUDcVhwleSw0hpMSZtnP84+1uz7+ES1GILenwFhvLE7DTG6PXkDhq0/H24N4Ml6ZtUTdKMhDHhbcXhQpKCNxcu79rIeCiprs0t1T8EgBRV7Acaqrz8ph1ersOTsxPhTTE7mNtVUODdij2ujqueBKZTpfGQ\u003d\u003d"}]